afepower.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | aFe POWER

### Your privacy is important to us

Your privacy is very important to Advanced FLOW Engineering, and we are committed to protecting it. You are welcome to explore our web site without providing any information about yourself. When you visit and navigate our Web site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. By "personal information," we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, account address, e-mail account address or telephone number.

What information does Advanced FLOW Engineering collect from me? Our web server automatically recognizes your domain name. Our web server does not recognize your e-mail account address. Most of Advanced FLOW Engineering web site has been designed to not require the use of any personal identifiers (such as name, account address, telephone number or e-mail account address). IF YOU SEND US AN E-MAIL OR SUBSCRIBE TO A NEWSLETTTER, WE WILL HAVE YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS AT OUR SITE.

Advanced FLOW Engineering collects and uses certain information on its web site. This information includes your IP account address, information about your browser (i.e., whether you are using Netscape, Internet Explorer, etc.), and information about your Internet Service Provider (i.e., AOL, Verizon). An IP account address (Internet Protocol Address) is a unique number that is used to represent every single computer in a network. All computers on the Internet have a unique IP account address. None of the foregoing information will be used by Advanced FLOW Engineering in any way, or in connection with any other information, to identify you personally.

Advanced FLOW Engineering uses the statistical information gathered about you and all of its users for internal statistical purposes only, e.g., to track where users go on the web site. This information is not linked to specifically identifiable individuals. This type of information will be used to aid Advanced FLOW Engineering in adding information to its web site that will be useful for site users and that will improve the performance of our web site.

### Emails

When you sign up for free e-mails, we maintain information about your selections only for the purpose of sending you the e-mails. We do not use identifying personal information for any other purpose although it may be included in anonymous, aggregated statistical information. If you communicate with us by email you should understand that email is not secure against interception. If your communication includes sensitive or confidential information, please contact us by phone or mail.

Instructions for unsubscribing from e-mails are located at the bottom of each e-mail. Click the link given and request to be removed from our list.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive, not on our site.

We do not use cookies on our site and will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.

### Disclosure of your information

All of the information you choose to provide us is absolutely confidential and voluntary. We will never give, sell, rent or reveal your name or account address (including e-mail) to any outside party without your express consent. Advanced FLOW Engineering will not disclose your personally identifiable information to independent third parties other than those who help us operate our site, (such as an independent third party who might help us deliver our newsletters).

When you sign up for these member services we will share your name, contact information or other information necessary for the third party to provide the services. These independent third parties will only use your information to provide the designated service, and will handle your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Security measures

Advanced FLOW Engineering takes reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information. When users submit personally identifiable information, it is protected both on-line and off-line. We use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption protocol during transfer of any sensitive information.

### Notification of changes

We will prominently post any significant changes we make to our Privacy Policy. Advanced FLOW Engineering will use the information collected from you in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was collected.

### Links to other web sites

This site contains links to other sites. Advanced FLOW Engineering is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

### Correcting and updating information

If, at any time, a correction needs to be made to existing personal information that you have voluntarily provided to the web site, users may email the webmaster at tech@afepower.com and request that the information be changed or deleted.

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to tech@afepower.com.

### Copyright information

All content at Advanced FLOW Engineering, including graphics, logos, icons, text, and images, is the property of Advanced FLOW Engineering and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.
